Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
It's not that.
It's a promise.
I'm tired of saying that.
Let's practice.
I'm in charge of betrayal.
You are.
I can only say one word.
Today,
we played
a game of betrayal.
I'm in charge of betrayal.
The rule is
the one who says 100 words will lose.
Each person will say
3 words.
The one who says 100 words
will lose.
I see.
It's not good to end the game
by saying 100 words.
I prepared Umeboshi and lemon juice.
I see.
The number of times you say the number
will be the number of times
you put lemon juice on Umeboshi.
The last person to say 100 words
will eat Umeboshi.
I see.
Why are you happy?
I didn't hear that.
I see.
For example,
what are you doing?
Are you ready?
Yes.
The one who plays rock-paper-scissors
will say 100 words.
Look at the screen.
This way?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I'll say G.
I'll say C.
I'll say P.
I'll say F.
I'll say H.
I'll say J.
I'll say M.
I'll say Q.
She's attacking directly.
She's fast.
I'll say 7.
I'll say 8.
I'll say 9.
I'll say 10.
She's not nervous.
She's too fast.
I'll say 14, 15, 16.
Go for it!
I'll say 16.
I'll say 17.
I'll say 18.
I'll say 20.
You said 4.
I'll say 21, 22, 23.
I'll say 23.
I'm sorry.
I'll say 24, 25, 26.
This is fun.
I'll say 27, 28, 29, 30.
I'll say 31, 32, 33.
I'll say 34, 35, 36.
She's cute.
I'll say 37, 38, 39.
She's been like this.
Which one did you say?
I'll say 37, 38, 39.
No, 41.
I'll say 42.
She's talking.
No, I'm not.
How far did you say?
I'll say 45.
I'll say 47.
I'll say 48.
No, I'll say 49.
I'll say 50.
I'll say 51.
She's a good woman.
She said 53.
I'll say 53.
I'll say 54, 55.
Why did you say that?
I'll say 56, 57, 58.
I'll say 59.
I'll say 60.
I'll say 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68.
What are you doing?
I'll say 69, 70, 71, 73, 74, 75.
I'll say 76, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83.
I'll say 84, 85, 86, 87.
I'm getting confused.
I'll say 88, 89, 91, 92.
I'll say 95, 96, 97, 98.
Who are you feeding this to?
I'm a guardian.
I'm a power girl.
You don't do that.
I'm sorry.
It's hard to do.
I'll say 98.
I'll say 100.
I'm sorry.
I'll say 99.
I'll say 99.1.
I'm sorry.
You're kind.
I'll say 100.
She said 100.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'll eat this.
I'll eat this first.
It's a good thing.
It's delicious.
I really like this.
Oh, it's not sour at all.
Oh, really?
Then, the next umeboshi is a little
open.
I see.
Direct assas
Thank you for watching.
Fukase There are
some parts where the
guy didn't work, so
it may be sour if I say Japanese
cucumbers.
Certainly I'm from
Shimizu Everyone
33, 32
34, 35
36, 37, 38
39, 40, 41
43, 44
40, 40, 40
Masaharu Koyama
40, 50, 50
You are Dandy
Thank you for watching.
Nice, Dandy
You said it yourself
Let's go.
It's a
good
feeling, but it's a
good feeling, isn't it?
98 times.
98 times?
So, Miyu will put it twice and eat it.
Or, I will put it in the microwave.
Or, everyone will eat it.
That's right.
You can put it once and then think
about it.
Yes.
Thank you.
Close your eyes.
Open your eyes in 3 seconds.
Put your eyes in front of yourself or
Ren.
3 seconds.
It depends on which one you choose.
You can choose the one you like.
Thank you.
It's OK.
It's sour.
It's not sour.
I wanted to drink this.
Next, put sugar in pancakes.
Sugar?
The answer is...
It's sour.
Now, you've got the answer.
What should we do?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
We've started the game, haven't we?
Let's change the order of the seats.
First, let's go with the lower one.
That's not the lower one!
I said the lower one.
1.
I can write it down three times.
I thought I could write it down only
100 times.
You're good at writing.
It's cute.
It looks cute, but it's not.
What?
What's this?
It's buried.
I can't see it anymore.
What?
I said 15.
I said 18.
Sorry.
I said 19.
Did you say it four times?
20 21 20
23 24 25
26 27 28
You are blinding me
29 30 31 32
34 35 36
In Mabuse style
31 39
What do you want to do in winter?
40 42
I'm full
Please subscribe to my channel!
I want to read and compare.
Let's read the normal one.
45? 46?
Thank you for watching!
49 50
51 What do you do with this?
What do you do with this?
You can cooperate with everyone and
reduce the number of people who can eat
it.
Ah, that's right.
But I don't eat it myself, so I'm going
to eat it.
I'm going to eat it.
Does it make sense to write?
I didn't know that all the bags were
here.
I'm just transferring sugar now.
I can't see it.
Pancake
I entered
I'm going to die.
It's a sugar that's good for your
health.
It's good for your body.
Please
I don't like it.
I like it.
Don't count.
I'm thinking.
I don't know the answer.
Wait, 94
9 o'clock.
Start with 9.
9!
Let's gather them.
Wait.
What's wrong with you?
Please.
Excuse me.
9!
100.
Really?
Yeah,
no,
space bubbles have entered.
I'm
sorry about
this.
go
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You don't have to eat it.
Are you okay?
It looks delicious.
It's sweet!
Did you eat a plum?
It's too late to say good-bye.
Pancake is made of sugar.
I still have sugar.
Which one is stronger? Sour or sweet?
What is this?
It's syrup.
It's like snow.
It's shaved ice.
Shaved ice?
Which one is stronger?
I think so, too.
bloom!
Oh, they're fighting.
Ah, it's sour.
But it's sweet.
It's sour.
Give me more tea.
It's Tachibana Goroku.
Do you need more tea?
That's water.
That's not water.
But...
The conclusion of today's Not 100 Games
is that sour is stronger.
The conclusion.
Anna, do your best.
Sour.
Sour won.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for watching!
Please look forward to next week!
Bye!
Sour! Sour!
Please look forward to next week!